Guide to the Rice University Past Faculty and Staff records, 1961-1996 UA 008
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VI: Past Faculty and Staff A-Z, 1953-1993, 166925
  - Willcott, M. Robert, III - Chemistry, 1981-1990; 170636 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Williams, Robert P. - Biology, 1985-1989; 170692 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Williamson, James - Architecture, 1990; 170638 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Wilson, William R. - Administration/Psychology, 1984-1991; 170639 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Winter, Thomas G. - Physics, 1991; 170640 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Wolin, Judith - Architecture, 1988-1990; 170641 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Wornardt, Walter W. - Geology and Geophysics, 1989-1992; 170642 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Wynn, Charles - History, 1988-1989; 170643 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Xu, Peijun - Mathematics, 1990-1991; 170644 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Yang, Deane - Mathematics, 1983-1990; 170645 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Zdatny, Steven M. - History, 1986-1989; 170646 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Zhang, Yin - Mathematical Sciences, 1988-1990; 170647 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Series VII: Past Faculty and Staff A-Z, 1946-2013, 170648
  - Adve, Sarita - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1993-2001; 170649 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Akers, W.W. - Chemical Engineering, 1962-1996; 170650 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Akover, Madeleine - French Studies, 1975-2004; 170651 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Alcover, Madeleine - French Studies (working), 1980-2001; 170652 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Anderson, Shannon - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 2002-2010; 170653 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Angel, Yves - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1983-2007; 170654 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Anvari, Bahman - Bioengineering, 1998-2009; 170655 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Apple, Max - English, 1972-2002; 170656 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Applegate, David - Computational and Applied Mathematics, 1996-2000; 170657 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Armeniades, Constantine - Chemical Engineering, 1969-2009; 170658 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Arpaly, Nomy - Philosophy, 1994-2003; 170659 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Athanasiou, Kyriacos - Bioengineering, 2000-2009; 170660 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Austin, Joe - Education, 1979-2001; 170661 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Auston, David H. - Provost/Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1994-1999; 170662 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Avé Lallemant, Hans - Geology and Geophysics, 1969-2006; 170663 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Badgwell, Thomas - Chemical Engineering, 1993-2010; 170664 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Bagozzi, Richard P. - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 2000-2005; 170665 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Bailar, Benjamin - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 1987-1997; 170666 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Baker, Lovett - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 1986-2006; 170667 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Baker, Stephen - Physics, 1963-2004; 170668 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Bally, Albert - Geology and Geophysics, 1981-1996; 170669 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Barland, Ian - Computer Science, 1997-2005; 170670 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Barlow, Stephen - Linguistics, 1992-2004; 170671 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Barnea, Amir - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 1993-1998; 170672 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Barnea, Amir (working) - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 1989-1998; 170673 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Barut, Yasar - Economics, 1998-2002; 170674 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Basak, Chandramallika - Psychology, 2009-2011; 170675 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Beal, Daniel J. - Psychology, 2004-2012; 170676 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Bearden, Francis - Human Performance and Health Sciences, 1954-2000; 170677 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Behar, Victor - Chemistry, 1998-2006; 170678 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Bell, Michael - Architecture, 1993-2000; 170679 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Bennett, John - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1988-2000; 170680 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Bennett, Sherry - Political Science, 1994-2000; 170681 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Berman, Eli - Economics (1 of 2), 2001-2002; 170682 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Berman, Eli - Economics (2 of 2), 2001-2002; 170683 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Berndt, Jerry - Athletics, 1986-1988; 170685 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Bixby, Robert - Computational and Applied Mathematics, 1983-2010; 170684 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Bland, R. L. - Health and Physical Education, 1962-1995; 170686 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Bledsoe, Robert S. - German and Slavic Studies, 1994-1999; 170687 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Blin, John - Architecture, 1998-2006; 170688 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Bolech, Carlos J. - Physics and Astronomy, 2005-2010; 170689 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Bondos, Sarah - Biochemistry and Cell Biology, 1999-2010; 170690 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Bonner, Billy - Physics, 1981-2009; 170691 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Bourland, Hardy - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1974-2000; 170693 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Bowern, Claire - Linguistics, 2004-2010; 170694 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Bowers, Jeffrey - Psychology, 1993-1998; 170695 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Branton, Regina - Political Science, 2000-2011; 170696 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Brelsford, John - Psychology, 1970-2005; 170697 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Brenner, Lyle - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 2000-2001; 170699 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Brotzen, Franz R. - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1954-2008; 170698 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Brown, David P. - Architecture, 1996-2004; 170700 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Brown, David S. - Political Science, 1997-2002; 170701 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Brown, Judith - Dean of Humanities, 1995-2000; 170702 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Brown, Lee - School of Social Sciences, 2002-2004; 170703 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Brown, Lee - Sociology, 1995-1997; 170704 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Burgund, E. Darcy - Psychology, 1995-1997; 170705 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Burt, George - Shepherd School of Music, 1984-1997; 170706 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Busby, George - Chemistry, 1989-1996; 170707 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Bush, George H. W. - Political Science, 1990; 170708 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Caflisch, Anna - French Studies, 1983-2002; 170709 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Callahan, Daniel - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1990-1997; 170710 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Camfield, William - Art and Art History, 1969-2002; 170711 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Camp, Stephanie - History, 2009-2010; 170712 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Campbell, James - Biochemistry and Cell Biology, 1959-2002; 170713 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Carle, Allan - Computational and Applied Mathematics, 1998-2006; 170714 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Carrington, Samuel - French Studies, 1967-1996; 170715 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Cavallini, Felicia - Human Performance and Health Science, 1996-2001; 170716 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Chae, Suchan - Economics, 1985-2009; 170717 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Chang, Yoosoon - Economics, 1995-2006; 170718 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Chapman, Alan J. - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1946-2007; 170719 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Cheatham, John B. - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1963-1996; 170720 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Choi, Hyeokho - Electrical and Chemical Engineering, 2000-2006; 170721 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Cohen, Ruben - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1985-1994; 170722 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Colbert, Daniel - Chemistry, 1993-2003; 170723 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Collis, S. Scott - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1996-2003; 170724 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Cook, William - Computational and Applied Mathematics, 1994-2001; 170725 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Conte, Joel - Civil Engineering, 1990-1997; 170726 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Copeland, James - Linguistics, 1966-2007; 170727 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Cordoba, Juan Carlos - Economics, 2001-2009; 170728 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Costello, Kathryn - Vice President of Development, 1994-1998; 170729 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Covington, Michael - Biochemistry and Cell Biology, 2008-2011; 170730 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Curl, Robert - Chemistry (1 of 2), 1958-2008; 170731 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Curl, Robert - Chemistry (2 of 2), 1958-2008; 170732 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Currall, Steven - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 1993-2007; 170733 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Cyprus, Joel - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1977-2000; 170734 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Daichman, Graciela - Hispanic and Classical Studies, 1975-1999; 170735 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Dailey, Jane - History, 1994-2000; 170736 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Dakoulas, Panajiotis L. - Civil Engineering, 1987-2002; 170737 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Daley, Michele J. - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 1994-2003; 170738 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Davidson, Chandler - Sociology (1 of 2), 1966-2003; 170739 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Davidson, Chandler - Sociology (2 of 2), 1966-2003; 170740 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Davis, Philip W. - Linguistics, 1969-2003; 170741 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Davis, Sam - Chemical Engineering, 1957-2006; 170742 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Dawson, Clint - Computational and Applied Mathematics, 1991-1995; 170743 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Dean, Nathaniel - Computational and Applied Mathematics, 1998-2003; 170744 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - De Bremaecker, Jean-Claude, 1959-1994; 170745 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - DeClippel, Geoffrey - Economics, 2005-2007; 170746 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - de Hostos, Eugenio - Biochemistry and Cell Biology, 1995-1998; 170747 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Dennis, John - Computational and Applied Mathematics, 1979-2002; 170748 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - DeRose, Keith - Philosophy, 1993-1998; 170749 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Dharan, Bala - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 1982-2009; 170750 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Dietz, Elizabeth A. - English, 2002-2005; 170751 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Dillon, Diane - Art and Art History, 1993-1996; 170752 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - DiPalma, Vittoria - Art and Art History, 2003-2005; 170753 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Dipboye, Robert - Psychology, 1978-2004; 170754 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Dix, Robert H. - Political Science, 1967-1998; 170755 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Djidjev, Hristo - Computer Science, 1991-1997; 170756 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Donato, Katherine - Sociology (1 of 2), 2000-2006; 170757 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Donato, Katherine - Sociology (2 of 2), 2000-2006; 170758 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Doughtie, Edward O. - English, 1963-2001; 170759 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Downing, Christopher T. - Jones Graduate School of Management, 2004-2007; 170760 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Drew, Katherine Fischer - History, 1950-1996; 170761 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Druschel, Peter - Computer Science, 1994-2006; 170762 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Dubay, Brenda - Art and Art History, 1987-1998; 170763 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Duck, Ian - Physics (1 of 2), 1963-2008; 170764 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Duck, Ian - Physics (2 of 2), 1963-2008; 170765 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Dunbar, Robert - Geology and Geophysics, 1981-1997; 170766 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Durrani, Ahmad - Civil Engineering, 1982-2008; 170767 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Dyson, Derek - Chemical Engineering, 1966-2000; 170768 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Ehrenstein, Judy (Addie) - Psychology, 1993-1998; 170769 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Eifler, Margaret - German and Slavic Studies, 1973-2005; 170770 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Elhaik, Tarek - Anthropology, 2008-2010; 170771 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Erdelyi, Csaba - Shepherd School of Music, 1991-1995; 170772 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Eskin, Suzanne - Bioengineering, 1982-2003; 170773 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Estle, Thomas L. - Physics, 1967-1996; 170774 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Fagan, Michael - Computational and Applied Mathematics, 2000-2007; 170775 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Farokhi, Sohela - Architecture, 1998-2009; 170776 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Farwell, Joyce - Shepherd School of Music, 1994-2005; 170777 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Felleisen, Matthias - Computer Science, 1987-2002; 170778 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Few, Arthur - Space Physics and Astronomy (1 of 2), 1970-2008; 170779 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Few, Arthur - Space Physics and Astronomy (2 of 2), 1970-2008; 170780 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Fisher, Frank M., Jr. - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, 1963-2002; 170781 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Fishman, Tayla - History, 1988-1998; 170782 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Fliegel, Raphael - Shepherd School of Music, 1975-2005; 170783 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Forman, Robin - Mathematics, 1987-2010; 170784 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Foster, Kevin - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, 1999-2005; 170785 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Fraser, Matthew P. - Environmental Science and Engineering, 1998-2010; 170786 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Freeman, John - Space Physics and Astronomy, 1964-2000; 170787 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Fukuyama, Tohru - Chemistry, 1979-1995; 170788 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Fultz, Lucille - English, 1990-2007; 170789 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Furjan, Helene - Architecture, 2004-2005; 170790 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Gamard, Elysabeth - Architecture, 1990-1997; 170791 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Ghitalla, Armando A. - Shepherd School of Music, 1994-2001; 170792 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Gibson, Brian T. - Human Performance and Health Sciences, 2000-2013; 170793 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Gibson, Susan - Biochemistry and Cell Biology, 1993-2008; 170794 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Gildea, Spike - Linguistics, 1993-2000; 170795 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Glantz, Raymond - Biochemistry and Cell Biology, 1969-2006; 170796 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Glass, Graham - Provost's Office, 1967-2005; 170797 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Gockenbach, Mark - Computational and Applied Mathematics, 1979-1999; 170798 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Gonsalves, Joshua - English, 2006-2009; 170799 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Gonzalez-Stephan, Beatriz - Hispanic and Classical Studies, 1997; 170800 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Gordon, Chad - Sociology, 1970-2006; 170801 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Gordon, William E. - Natural Sciences, 1966-1986; 170802 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Goveas, Jacqueline - Chemical Engineering, 1998-2002; 170803 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Grant, Simon - Economics, 2002-2011; 170804 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Griebling, Lynn - Shepherd School of Music, 1983-1993; 170805 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Grob, Alan - English, 1961-2007; 170806 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Guthrie, David M. - Architecture, 1995-2008; 170807 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Hackerman, Norman - Chemistry/University President (1 of 2), 1970-2007; 170808 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Hackerman, Norman - Chemistry/University President (2 of 2), 1970-2007; 170809 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Harrigan, Timothy - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1993-1999; 170810 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Haskell, Thomas - History, 1970-2009; 170811 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Hammond, Michael P. - Shepherd School of Music (1 of 2), 1986-2001; 170812 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Hammond, Michael P. - Shepherd School of Music (2 of 2), 1986-2001; 170813 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Hansz, Ingrid - Hispanic and Classical Studies, 1987-2000; 170814 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Harcombe, Elnora (Nonie) - Center for Education, 1991-2013; 170815 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Harcombe, Paul - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, 1972-2007; 170816 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Harrell, Lynn - Shepherd School of Music, 2002-2009; 170817 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Harvey, F. Reese- Mathematics, 1968-2003; 170818 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Hasker, Kevin - Economics, 1998-2002; 170819 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Havens, Adrian Neil - Art and Art History, 1964-2000; 170820 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Haverkamp, Eva - History, 1999-2008; 170821 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Haymes, Robert - Space Physics and Astronomy, 1968-1998; 170822 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Hazelwood, C. F. - Biophysics, 1975-1994; 170823 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Heeley, Michael - Jones Graduate School of Management, 1999-2004; 170824 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Hellums, J. David - Chemical Engineering, 1960-1998, 2003-2005; 170825 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Henry, Charles - Computer Science, 2001-2007; 170826 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Henry, Charles - Vice Provost and University Librarian, 1996-2007; 170827 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Heymann, Dieter - Geology and Geophysics, 1966-1998; 170828 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Heeley, Michael B. - Jones Graduate School of Management, 1999-2004; 170829 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Hightower, Joe - Chemical Engineering, 1967-2001; 170830 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Hitchcock, Christopher - Philosophy, 1993-1995; 170831 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Hochstettler, Thomas - History, 1998-2004; 170832 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Holloway, Clyde - Shepherd School of Music, 1977-2010; 170833 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Howell, William C. - Psychology, 1970-1987; 170834 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Huddle, Don - Economics and Business, 1964-1992; 170836 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Huffer, Lynne - French Studies, 1998-2005; 170837 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Hughes, Joseph - Environmental Science and Engineering, 1992-2005; 170838 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Hwu, Shiou-Jyh - Chemistry, 1988-1995; 170839 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Hyde, E. McKay - Computational and Applied Mathematics, 2004-2007; 170840 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Hyman, Harold M. - History (1 of 2), 1968-1997; 170841 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Hyman, Harold M. - History (2 of 2), 1968-1997; 170842 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Ikenberry, David - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 1991-2003; 170843 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Ingersoll, Richard - Architecture, 1986-1998; 170851 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Isle, Walter W. - English, 1961-2007; 170852 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Jaber, Andrea - Shepherd School of Music, 1996-1998; 170853 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Jain, Neelam - Jones Graduate School of Management, 1999-2003; 170854 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Javeline, Debra - Political Science, 2000-2004; 170855 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Jenckes, Kate - Hispanic Studies, 2003-2005; 170856 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Jett, Quintus - Jones Graduate School of Management, 1999-2003; 170857 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Jimenez, Carlos - Architecture, 1994; 170858 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Johnson, Don - Electrical and Computer Engineering/Statistics, 1977-2008; 170859 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Jones, Samuel - Shepherd School of Music, 1973-1997; 170860 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Jump, J. Robert - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1968-2003; 170861 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Kaplan, Gregory - Religious Studies, 2001-2012; 170862 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Katz, Martha S. - Shepherd School of Music, 1996-2001; 170863 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Katz, Paul C. - Shepherd School of Music, 1996-2001; 170864 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Kecht, Maria-Regina - German Studies, 1997-2010; 170865 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Kelber, Werner - Religious Studies, 1973-2005; 170866 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Kelty, Christopher M. - Anthropology, 2001-2008; 170867 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Kennedy, Kenneth - Computer Science (1 of 2), 1971-2007; 170868 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Kennedy, Kenneth - Computer Science (2 of 2), 1971-2007; 170869 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Khabeshesku, Valery - Chemistry, 1991-2008; 170870 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Kim, Dae Il - Economics, 1992-1996; 170871 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Kinsey, James L. - Chemistry/Dean of Natural Sciences (1 of 2), 1987-2007; 170872 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Kinsey, James L. - Chemistry/Dean of Natural Sciences (2 of 2), 1987-2007; 170873 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Kiperman, Anita - Hispanic and Classical Studies, 1976-1998; 170874 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Klein, Lisa - Jones Graduate School of Management, 1999-2002; 170875 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Kobayashi, Riki - Chemical Engineering (1 of 2), 1951-1997; 170876 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Kobayashi, Riki - Chemical Engineering (1 of 2), 1951-1997; 170877 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Konisky, Jordan - Vice Provost for Research and Graduate Studies/Biochemistry, 1996-2007; 170878 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Krishnan, Trichy V. - Jones Graduate School of Management, 1997-2003; 170879 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Krumwiede, Keith - Architecture, 1996-2003; 170880 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Kumar, Piyush - Jones Graduate School of Management, 1996-2000; 170881 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Kwinter, Sanford - Architecture, 1993-2009; 170882 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Laibinis, Paul E. - Chemical Engineering, 2003-2005; 170883 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Lairson, Bruce - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1993-1997; 170884 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Lairson, David R. - Economics, 1977-2013; 170885 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Lally, Sean - Architecture, 2003-2009; 170886 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Lamb, Sydney - Linguistics, 1981-1998; 170887 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Landecker, Hannah - Anthropology, 2001-2008; 170888 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Landis, Chad - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 2000-2008; 170889 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Lane, Mary Ellen - Biochemistry, 2001-2009; 170890 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Last, Nana - Architecture, 1999-2000; 170891 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Laughery, Kenneth R. - Psychology (1 of 2), 1982-2002; 170892 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Laughery, Kenneth R. - Psychology (2 of 2), 1982-2002; 170893 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Leal, Maria Teresa - Spanish/Portuguese/Classics, 1965-1996; 170894 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Lee, Benjamin - Anthropology, 1995-2004; 170895 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Lee, Eva - Human Performance and Health Science, 1969-2000; 170896 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Leeman, William - Geology and Geophysics, 1977-2005; 170897 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Lichtenstein, Alex - History, 2002-2007; 170898 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Liebschner, Michael A. - Bioengineering, 2000-2008; 170899 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Lindsay, Bernard - Space Physics, 1999-2009; 170900 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Lindsay, D. Michael - Sociology, 2006-2011; 170901 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Longino, Helen E. - Philosophy, 1990-1995; 170902 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Love, Geoffrey - Jones Graduate School of Management, 2001-2002; 170903 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Luca, Sergiu - Shepherd School of Music, 1983-2010; 170904 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Lust-Okar, Ellen - Political Science, 1997-1999; 170905 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Lyandres, Evgeny - Jones Graduate School of Management, 2004-2008; 170906 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - MacKenzie, Kevin - Biochemistry and Cell Biology, 2000-2010; 170907 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - MacLeod, Mary Claire - Philosophy, 2000-2001; 170908 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Mancus, Dianne Sirna - Education, 1993-1994; 170909 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Mantzaris, Nikolaos - Chemical and Biomolecular Engineering, 2001-2009; 170910 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Marcus, George E. - Anthropology (1 of 2), 1975-2006; 170911 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Marcus, George E. - Anthropology (2 of 2), 1975-2006; 170912 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Margolis, Eric - Philosophy, 1995-2005; 170913 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Margrave, John - Chemistry (1 of 2), 1962-2003; 170914 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Margrave, John - Chemistry (2 of 2), 1962-2003; 170915 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Martin, William - Sociology (1 of 2), 1968-2005; 170916 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Martin, William - Sociology (2 of 2), 1968-2005; 170917 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Matusik, Sharon - Jones Graduate School of Management, 1998-2004; 170918 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - McEvilley, Thomas - Art and Art History, 1969-2005; 170919 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - McIntire, Larry Vern - Bioengineering (1 of 2), 1969-2003; 170920 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - McIntire, Larry Vern - Bioengineering (2 of 2), 1969-2003; 170921 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - McIntosh, Roderick J. - Anthropology (1 of 2), 1980-2006; 170922 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - McIntosh, Roderick J. - Anthropology (2 of 2), 1980-2006; 170923 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - McKeever, Matthew - Sociology, 1996-1997; 170924 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - McKenny, Gerald P. - Religious Studies, 1989-2001; 170925 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Meconi, Honey - Shepherd School of Music, 1987-2004; 170926 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Meffert, Lisa - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, 2000-2008; 170927 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Meixner, John - English, 1968-1995; 170928 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Mérida-Jiménez, Rafael - Hispanic and Classical Studies, 1998-2002; 170929 (Box 36, Folder 12)